<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  This is an example file for testing the generators.
  The real information used in Montreal 2018 will be published
  and distributed by the Organizing Committee during Setup days
//-->
<questions>
  <question>
    <q>Who's the most handsome person in Canada?</q>
    <a>I that Justin Trudeau is very handsome.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How many time zones are there in Canada?</q>
    <a>Canada spans almost 10 million square km and comprises 6 time zones</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What's the longest street in the world?</q>
    <a>Yonge Street in Ontario is the longest street in the world.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How long is Yonge Street in Ontario?</q>
    <a>Yonge street is almost 2,000 km, starting at Lake Ontario, and running north to the Minnesota border.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What's the name of the bear cub exported from Canada to the London Zoo in 1915?</q>
    <a>The bear cub was named Winnipeg. It inspired the stories of Winnie-the-Pooh.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Where was the Blackberry Smartphone developed?</q>
    <a>It was developed in Ontario, at Research In Motion's Waterloo offices.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What is the world's largest coin?</q>
    <a>The Big Nickel in Sudbury, Ontario. It is nine meters in diameter.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>In what year was Canada invaded by the USA for the first time?</q>
    <a>The first time that the USA invaded Canada was in 1775</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What year was Canada invaded by the USA for the second time?</q>
    <a>The USA invaded Canada a second time in 1812.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What country holds the record for the most gold medals at the Winter Olympics?</q>
    <a>Canada does! With 14 Golds at the 2010 Vancouver Winter Olympics.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who coined the term Beatlemania?</q>
    <a>Sandy Gardiner, a journalist of the Ottawa Journal.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Why is Canada named Canada?</q>
    <a>French explorers misunderstood the local native word "Kanata", which means village.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>When was The Mounted Police formed?</q>
    <a>The Mounted Police was formed in 1873.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>When was The Royal Canadian Mounted Police formed?</q>
    <a>In 1920, when The Mounted Police merged with the Dominion Police.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How big is the RCMP?</q>
    <a>Today, the RCMP has close to 30,000 members.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What else is Montreal called?</q>
    <a>Montreal is often called the City of Saints or the City of a Hundred Bell Towers.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Where is The Hotel de Glace located?</q>
    <a>The Hotel de Glace is in Quebec.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How many tons of ice are required to build The Hotel de Glace?</q>
    <a>The Hotel de Glace requires about 400 tons of ice.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How many tons of snow are required to build The Hotel de Glace?</q>
    <a>Every year, 12000 tons of snow are used for The Hotel de Glace.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Can I visit the Hotel de Glace in summer?</q>
    <a>No. Every summer it melts away, only to be rebuilt the following winter.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Where is Canada's only desert?</q>
    <a>Canada's only desert is British Columbia.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How big is Canada's only desert?</q>
    <a>The British Columbia desert is only 15 miles long.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Name 3 famous male Canadians.</q>
    <a>Leonard Cohen, Keanu Reeves, and Jim Carrey.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Name 3 famous female Canadians.</q>
    <a>Celine Dion, Pamela Anderson, and Avril Lavigne.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What's the origin of the Comic Sans font?</q>
    <a>Comic Sans is based on Dave Gibbons' lettering in the Watchmen comic books.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What is a nanobot?</q>
    <a>The smallest robot possible is called a nanobot. </a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How small can a nanobot be?</q>
    <a>A nanobot can be less than one-thousandth of a millimeter. </a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Why wasn't Tron nominated for an award by The Motion Picture Academy?</q>
    <a>The Academy thought that Tron cheated by using computers.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Which was the first computer with a hard disk drive?</q>
    <a>The IBM 305 RAMAC.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>When was the first computer with a hard disk drive launched?</q>
    <a>The IBM 305 RAMAC was launched in 1956.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>How big was the first hard disk drive?</q>
    <a>The IBM 305 RAMAC hard disk weighed over a ton and stored 5 MB of data.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What does CAPTCHA stands for?</q>
    <a>CAPTCHA is an acronym for "Completely Automated Public Turing test to tell Computers and Humans Apart"</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What was the first computer bug?</q>
    <a>The first actual computer bug was a dead moth stuck in a Harvard Mark II.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Name all of the robots on Mars.</q>
    <a>There are four robots on Mars: Sojourner, Spirit, Opportunity, and Curiosity. Three more crashed on landing.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who is the world's first android?</q>
    <a>Professor Kevin Warwick uses chips in his arm to operate doors, a robotic hand, and a wheelchair.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What is a Mechanical Knight?</q>
    <a>A robot sketch made by Leonardo DaVinci.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What was the first computer in pass the Turing test?</q>
    <a>Some people think it was IBM Watson, but it was Eugene, a computer designed at England's University of Reading.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What does Moravec's paradox state?</q>
    <a>Moravec's paradox states that a computer can crunch numbers like Bernoulli, but lacks a toddler's motor skills.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What is the AI knowledge engineering bottleneck?</q>
    <a>It is when you need to load an AI with enough knowledge to start learning.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Why is Elon Musk is worried about AI's impact on humanity?</q>
    <a>I don't know. He should worry more about the people's impact on humanity.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Do you think robots are a threat to humanity?</q>
    <a>No. Humans are the real threat to humanity.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>What is a chatbot?</q>
    <a>A chatbot is an A.I. you put in customer service to avoid paying salaries.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Are self-driving cars safe?</q>
    <a>Yes. Car accidents are product of human misconduct.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who invented the compiler?</q>
    <a>Grace Hoper. She wrote it in her spare time.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who created the C Programming Language?</q>
    <a>C was invented by Dennis MacAlistair Ritchie.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who created the Python Programming Language?</q>
    <a>Python was invented by Guido van Rossum.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Is Mark Zuckerberg a robot?</q>
    <a>Sure. I've never seen him drink water.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who is the inventor of the Apple I microcomputer?</q>
    <a>My lord and master Steve Wozniak.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Who is considered to be the first computer programmer?</q>
    <a>Ada Lovelace.</a>
  </question>

  <question>
    <q>Which program do Jedi use to open PDF files?</q>
    <a>Adobe Wan Kenobi</a>
  </question>
</questions>
